https://www.primeglobal.net/privacy

Login
Privacy PolicyPrimeGlobal is a worldwide association of independent accounting firms.PrimeGlobal does not and cannot offer any legal, accounting, tax, audit or other professional services or advice. Those services or advice may be offered by individual independent member firms of PrimeGlobal in their local jurisdictions. Each member of PrimeGlobal is a separate, distinct and independent entity. The relationship between PrimeGlobal and its independent members is not and shall not be construed as partners, associated companies, principal and agent, joint venture, or employer and employee. No member firm of PrimeGlobal is entitled to bind PrimeGlobal in any way.DisclaimerThe contents of this website, as they refer to PrimeGlobal, are for general information purposes only and do not constitute advice. PrimeGlobal believes the contents to be true and accurate as at the date of writing but can give no assurances or warranty regarding the accuracy, currency, or applicability of any of the contents in relation to specific situations and particular circumstances.This website is not intended to be a source for advice on legal, accounting or tax issues or otherwise and as such, the contents should not be relied upon by users of the website. Users should not act upon this information without seeking appropriate professional advice.   This website is not guaranteed to be free from any so-called computer viruses and it is strongly recommended that users check for such viruses before downloading any information from it to their computer equipment.PrimeGlobal may make changes to the material on the website at any time without notice. The material on the website may be out of date, and PrimeGlobal makes no commitment to update such material.The material on the website is provided “as is”, without any conditions, warranties or other terms of any kind. Accordingly, to the maximum extent permitted by law, PrimeGlobal provides users with the website on the basis that PrimeGlobal excludes all representations, warranties, conditions and other terms (including, without limitation, the conditions implied by law of satisfactory quality, fitness for purpose and the use of reasonable care and skill) which, but for this legal notice, might have effect in relation to the website.In addition, none of the content of this website will form any part of any contract between PrimeGlobal and the user or constitutes an offer by PrimeGlobal.LiabilityPrimeGlobal, any other party (whether or not involved in creating, producing, maintaining or delivering the website), and its officers, directors, partners, employees, shareholders or agents, exclude all liability and responsibility for any amount or kind of loss or damage that may result to a user or a third party (including without limitation, any direct, indirect, punitive or consequential loss or damages, or any loss of income, profits, goodwill, data, contracts, use of money, or loss or damages arising from or connected in any way to business interruption, and whether in tort (including without limitation negligence), contract or otherwise) in connection with the website in any way or in connection with the use, inability to use or the results of use of the website, any websites linked to the website or the material on such websites, including but not limited to loss or damage due to viruses that may infect the user’s computer equipment, software, data or other property on account of the user’s access to, use of, or browsing the website or their downloading of any material from the website or any websites linked to the website.If a user’s use of material on the website results in the need for servicing, repair or correction of equipment, software or data, the user assumes all costs thereof.PrimeGlobal Privacy Policy StatementOverviewPrimeGlobal is committed to protecting the privacy of the personal information of its clients, members vendors, partners and employees. We value the trust of the public and those we deal with, and recognize that maintaining this trust requires transparency and accountability in how we treat personal information that is shared with us. This Privacy Policy Statement (“Policy”) has been adopted to guide how we collect, use and disclose the personal information acquired during conducting our business and fulfilling our professional responsibilities.This Policy applies only to the PrimeGlobal web site. Please be aware that the PrimeGlobal web site may contain links to other sites, including sites maintained by PrimeGlobal member firms that are governed by other privacy statements that may differ somewhat and/or contain information as required under local law. We encourage users to review the privacy policy of each web site visited before disclosing any personal information.If you have any questions regarding this Policy, please contact webmaster services using the contact us link below.We adhere to the requirements of the law and our professional standards, and as we conduct our business operations, we frequently gather and use personal information. We seek consent to use this information when it is collected and recognize your expectation that it will be carefully protected. Our privacy practices require that we only use personal information outside of the original purpose for which it is collected after obtaining appropriate consent.Personal information is defined as any information that can be used to distinguish, identify or contact a specific individual, including information about age, income, opinions or beliefs, activities, habits, home location and family. However, business contact and other information about individuals that is available in the public domain, such as names, addresses and telephone numbers published in directories, are not considered personal information. Public information is not subject to privacy legislation and therefore is excluded from this policy and is not subject to the same protections as is the case with personal information. However, we do not disclose personal information about our staff, clients, members, vendors and partners without consent.We follow these policies when collecting, maintaining and using personal information:Collection and use of personal informationWe obtain personal information about you only if you choose to provide it, such as contact information to register for certain services and/or events. In some cases, you may have previously provided your personal information to PrimeGlobal (if, for example, you are a former employee). If you choose to register for PrimeGlobal information through a third party single sign-in service (e.g., LinkedIn, Google, or Twitter), we may collect any information or content needed for the registration that you permit the social media provider to share with us, such as your name and email address. Other information we collect may depend on the privacy settings you establish with your social media provider, so please review the privacy statement or policy of the applicable service. By registering and/or submitting personal information to PrimeGlobal, you are also agreeing to the use of this information in accordance with this Policy. Your personal information is not used for other purposes, unless we obtain your permission, or unless otherwise required or permitted by law or professional standards. For example, if you register on our web site and provide information about your preferences, we will use this information to personalize your user experience. If you send us a resume to apply online for a position with PrimeGlobal, we may use the information that you provide to match you with available PrimeGlobal job opportunities. By registering for conferences, we will obtain your permission to use your likeness in a photograph, video, or other digital media (“photo”) in any and all company publications, including web-based publications, without payment or other consideration. Additional information obtained with your consent, such as dietary restrictions and medical conditions, will be provided to vendors (hotels, restaurants, or venues utilized for PrimeGlobal events) solely for the protection of your personal choice, well-being and overall health, and safety.Sensitive Personal InformationPrimeGlobal generally collects only the personal information required to fulfil your request. If additional information is required, you will be notified of this at the point of collection. PrimeGlobal only collects "sensitive" personal information (i.e. personal information regarding a person's race, ethnicity, political beliefs, trade union membership, religious or similar beliefs, physical or mental health, sexual life or criminal record) if you voluntarily provide it to us, and only where it is required for a specific purpose, and is permitted to be collected by law or professional standards.Please do not provide sensitive personal information to PrimeGlobal, unless you consent to our use of that information for its legitimate business purposes and consent to the transfer and storage of the information to and in PrimeGlobal databases. If you question the necessity of providing sensitive information for any particular purpose, please contact us at privacy@primeglobal.net.ConsentYour consent is required for the collection and proposed use of personal information when information is collected. Consent can be either explicit or implied and can be provided directly to us by you or your authorized representative (such as you firm’s Managing Partner/Partner-In-Charge or Contact Partner). We require your explicit consent in writing or electronically for the use of your personal information.CookiesPrimeGlobal’s websites uses cookies to enable web site functions and for tracking performance.  PrimeGlobal’s policy governing our use of cookies can be found on our website HERE> Google AnalyticsThis website uses Google Analytics to track performance. For example, we may track visitor sessions and referral sources to our sites. We use this data to understand site performance to serve you better. We may also track the performance of promotional links to our site. No personal information is passed to Google Analytics. Note that Google Analytics stores its data within the United States of America and is therefore subject to US laws.  Those wishing to opt out of Google Analytics data collection should use the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.ChildrenPrimeGlobal understands the importance of protecting children's privacy, especially in an online environment. Our sites are not intentionally designed for, or directed at, anyone under the age of 18, and our policy is never to knowingly collect or maintain children’s information except where required as part of an engagement to provide professional services.Sharing and transfer of Personal InformationIn some instances, PrimeGlobal may share your personal information with outside companies, publications, service providers or vendors. This may include the transfer of this information across geographical borders to other PrimeGlobal member firms or third parties working with us or on our behalf to help fulfill your requests. PrimeGlobal may also store personal information in other legal jurisdictions. By providing personal information online to us, you are consenting to the transfer and/or storage of your personal information in this manner. PrimeGlobal does not sell personal information to any third parties, nor will PrimeGlobal transfer your personal information to any third parties for their own direct marketing use.Compliance with laws and regulationsPrimeGlobal may be required to disclose personal information in response to requests of government or law enforcement agencies or where disclosure is required by applicable laws, court orders, or government regulations. These disclosures may also be needed for data privacy or security audits and/or to investigate or respond to a complaint or security threat.ChoicesYou are not required to submit any personal information to PrimeGlobal online, but certain personal information may be required for you to receive additional information about our services and events. PrimeGlobal may also ask for your permission for certain uses of your personal information, and you can agree to or decline those uses. If you opt-in for particular services or to receive communications from us, you will be able to unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions included in each communication. Where you unsubscribe from a service or communication, we will try to remove your information promptly, but may require additional information to process your request.AccuracyPersonal information will be maintained as completely, accurately and up-to-date as possible. You are encouraged to review, correct and update personal information. Under most circumstances you have the right to reasonable access to your personal information to correct any inaccuracies. You can also make a request to update or remove information about you by contacting privacy@primeglobal.net and we will make all reasonable and practical efforts to comply with your request, so long as it is consistent with applicable law and professional standards.Information securityPrimeGlobal has reasonable security policies and procedures in place to protect personal information from unauthorized loss, misuse, alteration, or destruction. Appropriate physical and electronic measures are also used to help ensure that personal information is secure. To the best of our ability, access to your personal information is limited to those who require the information to fulfil their job responsibilities. Those individuals who have access to the data are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information. However, despite our best efforts, security cannot be absolutely guaranteed against all threats.Retention of personal informationPersonal information will not be used or disclosed for purposes other than those for which it has been collected, except with your consent or as required by law. We do not share personal information with unaffiliated third parties, except where necessary for legitimate professional and business needs, to carry out your requests, and/or as required and permitted by law or professional standards. We also make reasonable efforts only to retain personal information so long as it is necessary to comply with your request or you ask that the information be deleted.Changes to this policyPrimeGlobal may modify this Policy from time to time to advise of changes to our current privacy policies and practices. When changes are made to this Policy, the date of the update will be provided on this site, so we encourage you to review our site periodically for changes.Policy questions and enforcementPrimeGlobal is committed to protecting the online privacy of your personal information. If you have questions or comments about our administration of your personally identifiable information, please contact us by email at privacy@primeglobal.net or write to us at:Pedro FigueroaStandards & Compliance ManagerPrimeGlobal3235 Satellite Blvd., Bldg. 400 Ste. 300 Duluth, GA 30096 USAYou may also use this address to communicate any concerns you may have regarding compliance with our Privacy Policy Statement.
